- Two little bees~
-两只小蜜蜂啊
- Flying among the flowers~
-飞到花丛中啊
- Left they fly, right they fly~
-左飞飞，右飞飞
- Nice!
- Drink…
-漂亮
-喝…
- Two little bees~
-两只小蜜蜂啊
- Come on.
- Flying among the flowers~
-来
-飞到花丛中啊
- Left they fly~
-左飞飞
Drink up.
喝酒吧
President Lu, what are you up to?
卢总干啥呢？
- There's still booze left, come on…
- How about we each drink half?
-还剩酒呢，快…
-一人喝一半好不好？
Any more and it'll drink us to death.
再喝真的要醉死人的啊
What'd you spend your money coming here for?
你花钱来这干啥来了？
If you don't get drunk, you've wasted it. Come on.
不醉不是白花钱了吗？ 快
I'll drink for Brother Lu.
我替卢哥喝
Little sister-in-law's the one who looks out for big brother.
还是小嫂子向着哥啊
Little sister-in-law?
小嫂子？
Hey.
嗨
Wait for me a moment, Miss Shen.
妳等我一下，沉小姐
Wait for me.
等我一下
Come on, little sister-in-law.
来，小嫂子
Let's you and me drink.
咱俩喝
- One more round.
-再来一盘
Right now?
现在吗？
Is that alright…
方便…
Okay.
好
I'll come alone.
我一个人过来
Okay.
好
Wait for me.
妳等我
Who was that, President Lu?
谁呀，卢总？
Do I need to report to you?
我需要向妳汇报吗？
No. Just asking.
不用，随便问问
What's this supposed to mean?
这是啥意思？
Just a little something.
小意思
Miss Shen.
沉小姐
Get in.
上车
I really didn't expect you'd come to me on your own.
真没想到妳会主动找我啊
I've thought it through.
我想明白了
Yin Hong was creating an opportunity for me.
殷红是在给我创造机会
You won't have to stay in the dorm anymore.
妳以后不用再住宿舍了
That suite of mine at the Jinhao—
我在金豪那个套房
you can move in anytime you like.
妳随时可以过去住的啊
So tonight, you'll come to my place—
那么今晚妳去我那边
is that okay?
可以吗？
Could you come with me to my friend's first to pick up some books?
能先陪我去我朋友那拿几本书吗？
I need them for class tomorrow.
我明天上课要用
Sure.
可以啊
(Imperial Video Screening Room)
（皇朝录像厅）
Your friend's not home?
妳朋友不在啊？
She went home for a few days.
她这几天回家了
Have a seat for a bit.
你先坐一会吧
Okay.
好
I know this movie star well.
这个明星我很熟啊
We often go out for tea together.
我们经常一起出来喝茶的
Is that so?
是吗？
When there's time, I'll take you to Hong Kong.
有空带妳去香港
I'll introduce you to him.
把他介绍给妳认识
Weren't you going to look for something?
妳不要找东西吗？
Right.
对
I'll be back down in a bit.
那我一会下来
Have a seat.
你先坐
Okay.
好
Can I use that restroom?
那个洗手间可以用吗？
(Restroom)
（卫生间）
It's broken.
坏了
That restroom's broken.
这个洗手间坏了
Use the one on the second floor.
用二楼的吧
Okay.
好
This way.
这边
(Restroom)
（卫生间）
Did you find it?
找到没啊？
I don't know where I put it.
不知道放哪了
I still have to keep looking.
我还得再找找
It's alright.
没关系的啊
Here works just fine for me too.
我在妳这里也可以啊
What's wrong?
怎么了？
Feeling shy?
害羞了？
It's not like it's your first time.
又不是第一次
Just relax.
放轻松点
Miss Shen.
沉小姐
The difference between people and animals—
人和动物有什么区别
do you know what it is?
妳知道吗？
There's no difference.
没有区别的
People—
人
once they take off their clothes—
脱掉衣服之后
aren't they just animals?
不就是动物了吗？
I'm not an animal.
我不是动物
I'm a person.
我是人
I'm not an animal.
我不是动物
Screw you.
去你的
So it's a honey trap?
仙人跳啊？
Playing me?
搞我？
You dare play me?
妳敢搞我？
Playing me?
搞我？
Shen Mo!
沈墨
Are you okay?
妳没事吧？
It's an anesthetic.
麻药
We can't let him get away.
不能让他走
Screw you.
去你的
The phone…
听电话…
(Imperial Video Screening Room)
（皇朝录像厅）
I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm truly sorry.
真的对不起
If I've offended you two in any way—
我有什么得罪你们的地方
I apologize.
我跟你们道歉
You think an apology can fix what you've done?
你觉得你干过的事，道歉能解决吗？
This whole thing really is a misunderstanding.
这件事情真的是误会
I've always had the greatest respect for Miss Shen.
我一直很尊重沉小姐的
It was Yin Hong who kept lying to me.
是殷红一直骗我
She told me you were willing.
她說妳是愿意的
Here's what we'll do.
这样
You let me go—
你们放我走
there's an 800,000-yuan draft in my car.
我车上有一张八十万的汇票
Consider it my compensation to you.
就算是我补偿你们的
And this whole thing never happened.
这件事情就当没有发生过
I'm a man of my word.
我说到做到啊
You're going to stay right here today—
你今天就在这
and write down clearly everything you've done in Hualin.
把你在桦林都干过什么 清清楚楚地写下来
What do you want me to write?
你们想要我写什么？
You're still fucking playing dumb?
你他妈还装？
Is this the first time you've pulled this?
你是第一回干这种事吗？
Every day in Hualin—
我每天在桦林
I have a lot of people to meet.
要见很多人的
If I go missing—
如果我不见了
plenty of people will come looking for me right away.
马上就会有很多人来找我的
And another thing—
还有
when you made that call—
妳打电话的时候
my driver was right there.
我司机也在场的
So here's the deal—
这样
you let me go first—
你们先放我走
and I can treat this whole thing—
我可以把这件事情
as if it never happened.
当作没有发生过
Make the call.
打电话
Call your driver.
给你司机打电话
Tell him you're fine.
告诉他你没事
Have you two watched so many videotapes—
你们是不是录像带看多了
that your brains have rotted?
把脑子看坏了？
Kidnapping means prison, you know that?
绑架要坐牢的，知道吗？
Somebody, help…!
来人呀…
Make the call!
打电话！
I'll call…
我打…
I'll call.
我打
Hello? Xiao Luo.
喂？ 小罗
It's… it's nothing.
没…没事
I'm… I'm in…
我…我在…
I'm in the restroom.
我在洗手间
It's fine… really, it's fine.
没事…真没事
That's all.
就这样
If anything comes up, I'll call you again.
有什么事，我再给你电话
Okay, bye.
好，掰掰
What if he really tells them we kidnapped him?
他要真说咱是绑架怎么办？
Let's cash out the money.
把钱取出来吧
And get out of here.
咱们离开这
I want to cash this.
取钱
Cash all of it.
都取出来
Sorry, sir, this one can't be cashed.
不好意思啊，您这个取不了
Why not?
为啥？
This is a commercial draft payable on a fixed date.
您这个是定日付款的商业汇票
See, it says the 17th right here.
上面不写着17号吗？
It can only be cashed on that date.
规定日期才能取的
One moment, please.
您稍等一下
This man says he wants to cash this.
这个人说要取钱
Do you know the difference between people and animals?
你知道人和动物有什么区别吗？
People—
人
have to pay the price for what they've done.
得为自己做过的事付出代价
(Restroom)
（卫生间）
He lied to us.
他骗咱们
I almost got detained at the bank.
我差点让银行给扣下
That fucking bastard.
这他妈王八蛋
Get up.
起来
He's dead.
他死了
(Restroom)
（卫生间）
I'm the one who killed him.
人是我杀的
It's got nothing to do with you two.
跟你俩没关系
Why?
为啥呀？
We could've just cashed the money and left Hualin together, couldn't we?
咱们取了钱 一起离开桦林不就行了吗？
Do you still want to leave with me now?
你现在还愿意跟我一起走吗？
Go where?
去哪啊？
Somewhere nobody knows us.
去一个没人认识的地方
And live all over again.
重新活一次
Who's there?
谁呀？
What are you doing?
干啥呢？
Wang Yang.
王阳
It's a little hot.
有点热
I'll go get you your medicine.
我去给你拿药
We need to find a new place.
得找个新的地方
We can't stay here anymore.
不能再住这了
We'll lie low for a while, and once we get the money we'll come find you.
我们先躲一躲，等拿到钱了再去找你
Go on back.
回去吧
Get a good night's sleep.
好好睡一觉
Just think of it as a dream.
就当是作了一场梦
Wouldn't it be nice if it really were a dream?
要真是个梦多好啊？
You wake up and nothing's changed.
醒了什么都没变
Nothing will change.
不会变
Nothing will ever change.
什么都不会变
(Imperial Video Screening Room)
（皇朝录像厅）
What are you here for?
妳来干嘛？
Still angry?
还生气呢
It's not that serious, is it?
不至于吧？
Your handkerchief and your brother's clothes—I've washed them all clean.
妳的手绢、妳弟的衣服都洗干净了
Just leave them there.
放那吧
Where are you off to?
这是要去哪啊？
Nowhere.
不去哪
You should go. I've got things to do.
妳走吧，我还有事
What things?
啥事啊？
You're not going to Hong Kong with President Lu, are you?
不是要跟卢总去香港吧？
Quit pretending.
别装了
When you called to set up that meeting with President Lu—
妳打电话约卢总的时候
I heard all of it.
我都听到了
So what?
怎么的？
Figured it out, have you?
想明白了？
How much is he paying you?
他给妳多少钱啊？
800,000.
八十万
Never seen that much money before, have you?
没见过这么多钱吧？
College girls really are a different fucking breed.
大学生还真他妈不一样啊
Lu Wenzhong handing you that kind of money—
卢文仲给妳这么多钱
your little boyfriend doesn't know, does he?
妳那小男朋友不知道吧？
No, he doesn't.
不知道
You really know how to play the game.
还是妳会玩
You get to have it all.
什么都让妳占了
He doesn't know now—
他现在不知道
but that doesn't mean he won't find out later.
不一定以后就不知道
Don't get me wrong.
别误会
I'm not threatening you.
我可不是威胁妳
Coming into this fortune—
妳发这笔财
shouldn't you be thanking me?
是不是应该感谢我？
Take it.
妳拿走吧
Isn't it me you wanted to become?
妳不是想变成我吗？
Take this, and you can become me.
拿走这个，妳就可以变成我了
Then I won't stand on ceremony.
那我可不跟妳客气了
Thanks.
谢了
You fucking bitch—
妳他妈的
Was Yin Hong here?
殷红来了？
Why did you do it?
为什么这么做？
Yin Hong is gone.
殷红没了
She's me now.
她现在是我了
Once you're dead, you don't have to believe in fate anymore.
人死了就不用再信命了
Stop looking for Wang Yang.
别再找王阳了
He can go on living a good life.
他可以好好活着
A bowl of wontons, please.
来碗馄饨
All out. That guy bought up the last three bowls.
没有了，最后三碗全让他包圆了
Thanks.
谢谢啊